

## Syed Muhámmad Saglain

### Contact

+92 300 0580479

saqlainprinters

## Skills

Redux Toolkit Webpack / Rollup

Javasciprt - ES6/ES7+ Typescript

Node.IS **ExpressJS** SocketIO

Git Github Object Oriented Programming

**Firebase** 

Firestore | Authentication API Integration Heroku / Netlify

## About me

I'm Saalain an ambitious problem solver with a passion for learning and implementing new solutions, and who would like to join a team of like-minded developers. Experienced in creating logical and innovative solutions of complex problems.

My goal is to climb the ladder and become one of the leading experts in my field, and want to be a part of something bigger.

## Education

2019-Current

**BS:SE University of Karachi** 

Intermediate Adamjee Govt Science College 2016

Matriculation

# **Work Experience**

2021 - Current

#### Dechains

Role: Senior Frontend Developer, I was responsible for creating whole responsive frontend of various blockchain related apps like NFT Markeplaces etc. While integrating and working on modularized custom libraries for apis and blockchain communication, Libs being compiled with webpack and rollup

2020 - 2021

## Slectus (US)

Multivendor ecommerce style platform with commision support and a complex profile and product management system and realtime features, MERN Stack App. Role: Frontend Developer, responsible for all the frontend work and integrations on the platform, little backend development authorized.

2020 - 2020

### **Novasoft**

Software House.

Role: Frontend Developer, responsible for most of the frontend work and integrations on their multiple projects in works.

1 Year

**Al-Raheem Printing Services** 

Role: Graphics Designer

## 3rd Party Projects

Some of many third party app i have developed as a developer

NFT-Crypto web apps on ReactJS

Apple Mapkit React App Firebase Data and Auth applications

Social Links sharing apps with NFC tag functionality Many of my projects can be viewed on my webportfolio https://saqlain1020.com

#### Extras

Fiverr freelancina experience Cartificates:-

- Webicamp module winner
- Graphics desiging from Arena Multimedia
- Envolpment Modeling Workshop participation by Comstech of OIC